A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Publications FA767
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Publications
1936-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
FA767
34.6 Cubic Feet 45 manuscript boxes, 4 standard record storage cartons
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
All published material is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Completion of a use agreement is required prior to providing scholarly access. See RAC Head of Reference (or applicable designee) for details.
Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Contains Ford Foundation publication such as the Ford Foundation Letter and the Ford Foundation report, other published reports, and conference papers.
Arrangement
Loosely arranged chronologically by publication.
Related Materials
Ford Foundation records, Publications (Non-Grant Related), Accessions 2017:079 and 2017:089 (FA1394) http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1394/collection
Ford Foundation records, Publications (Non-Grant Related), Accession 2017:050 (FA1304) http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1304/collection
Ford Foundation records, Special Collections Publications (FA1395) http://dimes.rockarch.org/FA1395/collection
- Ford Foundation publications, 1936-2010; 1
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 1, number 1-6, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 2, number 1-8, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 3, number 1-8, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 4, number 1-8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 5, number 1-8, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 6, number 1-7, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 7, number 1-7, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 8, number 1-6, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 9, number 1-6, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 10, number 1-6, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes special issue, "Not the Ford Foundation Letter", May 31,1979 (volume 0, number 1), in honor of McGeorge Bundy at his retirement from the Ford Foundation.
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 11, number 1-6, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 12, number 1-6, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 13, number 1-6, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 14, number 1-6, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 15, number 1-6, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 16, number 1-6, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 17, number 1-6, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 18, number 1-6, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 19, number 1-4, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 20, number 1-3, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 21, number 1-3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, volume 22, number 1-3, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 23, number 1-4, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 24, number 1-4, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 25, number 1-3, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 26, number 1-3, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 27, number 1-3, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 28, number 1-3, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 29, number 1-3, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 30, number 1-3, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 31, number 1-4, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 32, number 1-4, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 33, number 1-4, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 34, number 1-4, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 35, number 1-4, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Ford Foundation Report, volume 36, number 1-4, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Ford Reports: The Ford Foundation Magazine of Ideas and Action, number 1-2, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1964 January 15 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1964 May 15 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1964 December 18 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1965 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1965 November 30 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1966 February 11 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation, 1966 April 8 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 23, 1966 August 15 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 24, 1966 December (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Editorial Comment on Fourth Installment "Tax-Exempt Foundations and Charitable Trusts: Their Impact on Our Economy" (Wright Patman) Subcommittee, House of Representatives, 1966 December 21 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 26, 1967 June (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 29, 1967 December (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 30, 1968 March (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 31, 1968 June (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 32, 1968 September (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the dispute over New York City public schools, and the Ford Foundation's role therein, 1968 December (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 34, 1969 February (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation in connection with the Ways Means Committee hearing on foundations, 1969 April (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 35, 1969 May (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 36, 1969 August (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation in connection with the Ways Means Committee legislation affecting foundations, 1969 August (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the pending Congressional legislation affecting foundations, 1969 September 18 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the pending Congressional legislation affecting foundations, 1969 October 6 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the pending Congressional legislation affecting foundations, 1969 October 22 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Richard Magat memorandum re: editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation; Issue number 37, 1970 January (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 38, 1970 April (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Includes editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation.
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 39, 1970 June (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 40, 1970 October (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 41, 1971 February (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 42, 1971 April (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 43, 1971 July (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 44, 1971 October (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 45, 1971 December (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 46, 1972 March (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 47, 1972 May (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 48, 1972 October (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 49, 1973 February (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 50, 1973 June (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 51, 1973 September (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 52, 1974 March (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Current Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 53, 1974 May (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 54, 1974 October (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, Special Issue, number 55, 1974 November (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Includes editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation. This special issue deals with newspaper and magazine coverage of the Ford Foundation's financial conditions following on the New York Times article.
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 56, 1975 February (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 57, 1975 June (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 58, 1975 October (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 59, 1976 March (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 61, 1977 January (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, Special Issue, number 62, 1977 February (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Includes editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation. This special issue deals with newspaper and magazine coverage a press seminar held in conjunction with public release of the Greep Report (Reproduction and Human Welfare: A Challenge to Research).
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 64, 1977 May (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 65, 1977 September (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 66, 1978 January (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 67, 1978 June (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 68, 1978 September (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 69, 1979 January (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, Special Issue, number 70, 1979 March (Box 7, Folder 56)
    Includes editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation. This special issue deals with media coverage of the election of Franklin A. Thomas as President of the Ford Foundation.
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 71, 1979 June (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 72, 1979 December (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, Special Issue, number 73, 1979 December (Box 7, Folder 57)
    Includes editorials, selected newspaper feature articles and other comments about the Ford Foundation. This special issue deals with media coverage of the publication of the Ford Foundation sponsored report "Energy: The Next Twenty Years".
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 74, 1980 May (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 75, 1980 December (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 76, 1981 May (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 77, 1982 March (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 78, 1982 August (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 79, 1983 July (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 80, 1984 February (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 81, 1984 October (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 82, 1985 April (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 83, 1985 November (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 84, 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Comment on the Ford Foundation, number 85, 1986 November (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Perspectives USA, number 1 (Pilot Issue), 1952 January (Box 8, Folder 64)
    Pilot issue of proposed magazine, prepared and published for the Ford Foundation by James Laughlin.
  - Perspectives USA, number 2, 1953 Winter (Box 8, Folder 65)
    Published quarterly by Intercultural Publications Inc.
  - Perspectives USA, number 3, 1953 Spring (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Perspectives USA, number 4, 1953 Summer (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Perspectives USA, number 5, 1953 Fall (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Perspectives USA, number 6, 1954 Winter (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Perspectives USA, number 7, 1954 Spring (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Perspectives USA, number 9, 1954 Autumn (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Perspectives USA, number 10, 1955 Winter (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Perspectives USA, number 11, 1955 Spring (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Perspectives USA, number 12, 1955 Summer (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Perspectives USA, number 13, 1955 Autumn (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Perspectives USA, number 14, 1956 Winter (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Perspectives USA, number 15, 1956 Spring (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Perspectives USA, number 16, 1956 Summer (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Office for Asia and the Pacific, Annual Report, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Bangkok, Thailand Field Office, Annual Report, 1968 February-October (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Bangkok, Thailand Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Bangkok, Thailand Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - [Bogota] Office for Colombia and Venezuela, Annual Report, FY, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - [Bogota] Office for Colombia and Venezuela, Annual Report, FY, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 84, 85)
  - [Bogota] Office for Colombia and Venezuela, Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - [Bogota] Office for Colombia and Venezuela, Annual Report, FY, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Dacca/Dhaka, Bangladesh Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Dacca/Dhaka, Bangladesh Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Dacca/Dhaka, Bangladesh Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Dacca/Dhaka, Bangladesh Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - East Asia Program, Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Office for Eastern and Southern Africa, Annual Report, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - Office for Eastern and Southern Africa, Annual Report, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia Field Office Annual Project Status Report, FY, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia Field Office Annual Project Status Report, FY, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Jakarta, Indonesia Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - [Lagos, Nigeria] West Africa Program Report, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - [Lagos, Nigeria] West Africa Program Report, FY, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - [Lagos, Nigeria] West Africa Program Quarterly Report, 1974 October-December (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Activities in Latin America and the Caribbean, FY, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - Activities in Latin America and the Caribbean, FY, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - Activities in Latin America and the Caribbean, FY, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean, Report, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Lima, Peru Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Lima, Peru Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Mexico City Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    Includes budget plans for FY 1974-1975.
  - Middle East and Africa Program Summary Report, FY, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, FY, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, FY, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, Region-wide Summary, FY, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, Region-wide Summary, FY, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, FY, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Middle East and Africa Program Annual Report, FY, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Nairobi, Kenya Field Office Annual Report, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - [New Delhi] India and Nepal Program Status Report, 1961 October (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - [New Delhi] India and Nepal Program Status Report, 1963 October (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - [New Delhi] India and Nepal Program Status Report, 1964 October (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - The Ford Foundation in [New Delhi] India and Nepal: A Status of Activities Report, 1965 October (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - The Ford Foundation in [New Delhi] India and Nepal: A Status Report, 1966 October (Box 14, Folder 126, 127)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal, 1966 October (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - The Ford Foundation in [New Delhi] India and Nepal: A Status Report: Education, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - The Ford Foundation in [New Delhi] India and Nepal: A Status Report: Family Planning, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - The Ford Foundation in [New Delhi] India and Nepal: A Status Report: Management, Manpower, and Industry, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal: All Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal: Agriculture and Rural Development, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal: Economic Planning and Public Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal: Education, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal: Family Planning, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Status of Ford Foundation supported activities, [New Delhi] India and Nepal: Management, Manpower, and Industry, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: All Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 134, 135)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Agriculture and Rural Development, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Economic Planning and Public Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Education, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Family Planning, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Management, Manpower, and Industry, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: All Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Agriculture, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Education and Research, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Development, Planning and Management, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Status Report: Population, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Report, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 146)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 148)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 149)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - New Delhi, India Field Office Annual Report, FY, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - Santiago, Chile Field Office Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Office for South and Southeast Asia Program, Report, FY, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Office for Southeast Asia, Annual Report, FY, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - Tokyo, Japan Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - Tokyo, Japan Field Office, Annual Report, FY, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 159)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 161)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - [Tunis, Tunisia] North Africa Program Annual Report, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Reports' "President's Review" essays, 1979-1991 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - Ford Foundation Annual Reports' "President's Review" essays, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 165)
  - Ford Foundation Project Status Report, 1952 May (Box 17, Folder 166)